A Finding Aid to the Wilbur H. Burnham Studios Records, circa 1904-1991, in the Archives of American Art AAA.wilbhbur
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1916-1980s; Series 6; 10.6 Linear feet Boxes 2-12, 42
  732. Portland, OR-Holy Redeemer Church
  733. Jamaica Plain, MA-Pius Daughters Convent Chapel and New Chapel 1960
  734. Huntingdon, PA-Abbey Evangel. and Reformed Church
  735. Dayton, OH-St. Paul's Episcopal Church (not done)
  736. Wash. DC-Sts. Constantine and St. Helen Gr. Orth
  737. Cambridge-St. Peter's Catholic Church
  738. Tulsa, OK-Trinity Church, 2 door panels
  739. Randolph-Trinity Church, Rose-Christ the King
  740. Clarksville, TN-Trinity Church, Nativity
  741. Woods Hole-Ch. Messiah, 2 tower windows
  742. Edgewood, RI-Ch. Transfiguration
  743. Boston-Chapel, Children's Hospital
  744. Melrose-Methodist Church
  745. Houston, TX-St. Vincent de Paul
  746. Watertown, MA-Union Church
  747. Houston, TX-St. Stephen's Episcopal Church
  748. Glendale, CA-Forest Lawn Memorial Park
  749. Needham, MA-Christ Church
  750. Marblehead-St. Andrew's Church
  751. Tryon, NC-Tryon Presbyterian Church
  752. New York City-Church of the Epiphany
  753. Brighton-St. John's Seminary
  754. Wilmington, DE-Calvary Church
  755. Baltimore, MD-Cathedral of Mary Our Queen
  756. Toledo, OH-St. Michael's in the Hill
  757. New York, NY-South Wing, Riverside Church
  758. Braintee-Congregational Church
  759. Abilene, TX-Ch. Heavenly Rest
  760. Milton-St. Michael's Church
  761. Chattanooga, TN-First Presbyterian
  762. Denver, CO-Epiphany Episcopal Church
  763. Baltimore, MD-Cathedral Ch. Incarnation (Epis.)
  764. The Plains, VA-Grace Episcopal Church
  765. Honolulu, Hawaii-Central Union Church
  766. Springfield-Christ Church Cathedral
  767. Brookline-Levine Chapel
  768. Hamburg, NY-Methodist Church
  769. Melrose-Church of the Nazarene
  770. Clearwater, FL-Ch. Ascension
  771. Providence, RI-St. Pius Church
  772. Transparency-WHBjr. angel, 1962
  773. Chattanooga, TN-Cumberland Presby.
  774. New Rochelle, NY-St. Paul's Episcopal
  775. Washington, GA-First Meth. 8 Chapel
  776. Brookline-McKenny Home
  777. St. Joseph, MO-Mausoleum
  778. Colorado Springs-Chapel Holy Spirit
  779. Falmouth-St. Barnabas Memorial Church
  780. Melrose-Public Library
  781. Wakefield-Congregational Church
  782. Staten Island, NY, Chapel Daughters of St. Paul Convent
  783. Melrose, 1st Congregational Church
  784. Appleton, Wisconsin, Aid Association for Lutherans, A=Chapel, B=Ornamental Windows
  785. Worcester-Chestnut Street Congregational Church
  786. S. Weymouth, Church of Holy Nativity
  787. East Falmouth, MA, Grace Chapel
  788. East Greenwich, RI, St. Lukes
  789. Westford, MA, Hoffmire Residence
  790. Bengtz, T? 61 Clifton Park, Melrose (Finland)
  791. West Hartford, St, John's clerestory
  792. Bell
  793. [Quincy]
  794. Rot? Transparency
  795. Temple Israel
  796. Me? Cong.
  797. [Masonic em?] (WHB)
  798. Provincetown-Church of the Holy Virgin
  799. Queen of Hearts
  800. King of Hearts
  801. Lantern
  802?
  803?
  804. Peace Dale
  805. St. Pauls, Cambridge, Relief medallion
  806. Tivoli, NY
  807. Zodiac symbols
  808. Transparency-child and lamb
  809. Transparency-child and lamb
  810. Transparency-Madonna and child
  811. Transparency-[Penguin]
  812. Peace symbol-3 made
  813. Pisces-2 made
  814. Worcester-Higgins estate
  815. 4 door lights-Winthrop
  816. WHB
  817. Newfoundland
  818. Small Taurus
  819. Small Capricorn
  820. Houston
  821. Worcester-?
  822. Small Gemini
  823. Small Aries
  824. Small Virgo
  825. ?
  826. Sylvester Cape Cod
  827. [Cut one]
  828. ?
  829. Hamilton-Christ Church
  830. 4 Door ?
  831. Sample with Bro? ?
  832. Reading
  833. [Haywood Wakefield] Samples
  834. Sample with B? Christian
  835. Haywood Wakefield, colonial 9x20.5
  836. Haywood Wakefield, colonial 9x20.5
  837. Haywood Wakefield, colonial 10x24.5
  838. 9x9 samples Haywood Wakefield
  839. Marlboro-First Congr. Church
  840. Beverly-Hospital Chapel
  841. Belmont P? Park Congr.
  842. Heywood-6x26.5
  843. {Cab door lights (4)]
  844. Cleveland Church of the Saviour
  845. Sample Mirror-Heywood, Wakefield-6x31.5
  846. C? Wakefield
  847. Flowers transparency
  848. T? Repair
  849. Calami? (2 doors)
  850. F? 4 windows (house)
  851. Arlington ?
  852. Rounds-Wilmington
  854. Alley
  856. Providence-St. Stephens
  857. Q?-Salem Lutheran
  858. N. ? ? church
  858R. N. ? ? church repair
  859R. St. Steohen's Providence (repair)
  860. B?
  861. Newport
  862. Temple Israel B?
  864. McRuff?
  865. Lancaster, PA-Reformed Church
  866. Mr. Reese?
  867. England
  868. Daughter of St. Pauls
  870. 12 Christian Angels
  871. Rubiyat
  872. St. Paul's School Seal
  873. Lamp-?
  874. Old N. Church
  875. Old N. Church Silhouette
  876. ?-Silhouette
  878. England
  879. Rudeman
  880. [Hamilton-St. Pauls]
  881. [Beth Shalom Peabody]
  882. [Samples] Heyward Clear 9" x 38"
  883. [Samples] Heyward Clear 8" x 38"
  884. [Samples] Heyward Clear 13" x 38"
  885. Breckenridge House
  886. Concord, NH 4 chapel
  887. St. Georges School-Newport RI
  888. [Naffei]
  889-835. Blue and ? white
  890-837. Blue and ? white
  891-835. Window glass
  892-835. Window gladd
  893-835. ?, blue, window glass
  894-837. ?, blue, window glass
  895. ? repair
  896. Woods Hole repair
  897. Charlotte, Providence ?
  898. Bu???
  899. Still River, [MA]
  900. Belmont Payson Park
  901. Woods Hole Chancel repair
  902. ?
  903. Rogers-Portrait
  904. ?
  905. Choate seal for stars
  907. ? 6 doors
  908. ? [tulips]
  910R. St. ? ? window
  911. [Stella court Co.]
  912. Repair, Winchester Congr.
  913. Chattanooga 7 ?
  914. Milton Academy, seal
  915R. [Ewing Peabody]
  916R. Everett repair
  917. M?
  918R. Dr. Hard?
  919R. Pelegrine?
  920R. Schwartz repair
  924. ? St. Pauls
  925. Wakefield Baptist
  926R. T? repair
  927. ? St.
  928R. R? museum
  929R. Wilmington
  - Appraisals, 1940s-1960s (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Chas. Haas Company, 1950s-1960s (Box 2, Folder 27-30)
  - Contracts, Not Numbered, 1920s-1960s (Box 2, Folder 31-33)
  - Correspondence, 1922-1951 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - "Dead" Prospects, A, C, 1940s-1950s (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Index Cards of Locations and Materials, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 36)
    index cards housed in Box 42
  - Index Cards of Subjects with Job Numbers, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 37-39)
  - Notes on Transparencies Sent, 1950s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Numbered Lists of Contracts, #1-790, circa 1920s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Prospects, Y, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Repairs, A-C, E, 1940s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Repairs, F, G, L, 1950s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Repairs, M-N, P, T, W, 1940s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds, Francis & Rohnstock, Completed Contracts (Box 3)
    - Contracts, #106-174, 1921-1926 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Contracts, #175-209, 1927-1929 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Contracts, #213-245, 1930s (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, #401-499, 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Contracts, #500-592, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Contracts, #600-724, 1950s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Abilene, Texas, Church of the Heavenly Rest, 1950s-1970s (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Akron, OH, Immaculate Conception Church, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Albany, NY, Saint Andrew's Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
  - Albany, NY, Saint Paul's Church, 1940s (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - Albion, Michigan, Starr Commonwealth for Boys, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Arlington, MA, Pleasant Street Congregational Church, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Attleboro, MA, All Saints' Episcopal Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Auburndale, MA, Church of the Messiah, 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Austin, TX, Austin Presbyterian Theological, 1940s (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - A, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - Baltimore, MD, Cathedral of Mary our Queen, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Baltimore, MD, Cathedral of the Incarnation, 1950s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Baltimore, MD, Church of the Holy Nativity, 1950s-1960s (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bellau, France, Bellau Chapel, 1916-1930s (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Belmont, Massachusetts, All Saints' Episcopal Church, 1940s-1970s (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Beverly, MA, Beverly Hospital, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Beverly, MA, Saint Peter's Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bloomfield Hills, MI, Kirk in the Hills, 1940s-1970s (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - Bloomfield Hills, MI, Kirk in the Hills, 1940s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - Boston, MA, Boston University School of Theology, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Boston, MA, Greek Orthodox Cathedral of New England, 1940s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boston, MA, Old South Church in Boston, 1940s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boston, MA, Saint Clement's Church, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boston, MA, Saint Elizabeth's Hospital, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Braintree, MA, Emmanuel Church, 1930s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bridgeport, CT, First Methodist Episcopal Church, 1920s-1950s (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brighton, MA, Saint John's Seminary, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brighton, MA, Temple B'nai Moshe, 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
  - Bristol, RI, Saint Michael's Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bristol, TN, First Presbyterian Church, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bronxville, NY, Christ Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Brookline, MA, All Saints Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Brookline, MA, Leyden Congregational Church, 1920s-1930s (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Brookline, MA, Residence of S. Harvey McKenney, 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Brunswick, GA, Saint Mark's Episcopal Church, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - B, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 23-26)
  - Cambridge, MA, Episcopal Theological School, 1940s-1950s (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cambridge, MA, Saint James Episcopal Church, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Camp Lejeune, NC, Chapel, 1940s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Canton, OH, First Presbyterian Church, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Central Falls, RI, Saint George's Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Chappaqua, NY, Church of Saint Mary the Virgin, 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Charlotte, NC, First Presbyterian Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Charlotte, NC, Myers Park Baptist Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Charlotte, NC, Providence Baptist Church, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chattanooga, TN, Congregation B'nai Zion, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chattanooga, TN, First Cumberland Presbyterian Church, 1960s-1970s (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
  - Chattanooga, TN, First Cumberland Presbyterian Church, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Chattanooga, TN, First Presbyterian Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chestnut Hill, MA, Church of the Redeemer, 1920s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chestnut Hill, MA, First Church in Chestnut Hill, 1950s (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chevy Chase, MD, Chevy Chase Methodist Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - Chevy Chase, MD, Chevy Chase United Methodist Church, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chevy Chase, MD, Shrine of the Most Blessed Sacrament, 1920s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cincinnatti, OH, Calvary Church, Clifton, 1930s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Cincinnatti, OH, Wayside Cathedral, 1930s-1940s (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Clarksville, TN, Trinity Episcopal Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clayton, NY, Christ Episcopal Church, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clearwater, FL, Church of the Ascension, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Cleveland, OH, Church of the Covenant, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland, OH, Euclid Avenue Congregational Church, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland, OH, First Baptist Church, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland, OH, Our Lady of Peace Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland, OH, Saint Jerome's Church, 1950s (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cleveland, OH, Trinity Cathedral, 1930s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Clinton, MA, Saint John's Church, 1930s-1940s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Colorado Springs, CO, Chapel of the Holy Spirit, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Colorado Springs, CO, Church of the Holy Spirit, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Colorado Springs, CO, Grace Church and Saint Stephen's, 1940s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - Colorado Springs, CO, Grace Episcopal Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Colorado Springs, CO, Pauline Chapel, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Columbus, OH, Trinity Church, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 30-32)
  - Concord, NH, South Congregational Church, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Concord, MA, Trinity Church, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - C, Miscellaneous, 1930s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dedham, MA, Church of the Good Shepherd, 1940s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Denver, CO, Epiphany Episcopal Church, 1950s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Detroit, MI, Saint Mary of Redford Parish, 1920s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dobbs Ferry, NY, Ferncliff Chapel, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dorchester, MA, Saint Mary's Episcopal Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dover, NH, Saint Thomas's Church, 1920s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Durham, NC, Trinity Methodist Church, 1920s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - D, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - East Falmouth, MA, Grace Chapel, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Eaton Rapids, MI, Veterans of Foreign Wars National Home Chapel, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Elyria, OH, Saint Andrew's Church, 1930s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Evanston, IL, First Presbyterian Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - E, Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fall River, MA, Saint Mark's Episcopal Church, 1930s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Falmouth, MA, Saint Barnabas Memorial Church, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fitchburg, MA, Saint Bernard's Chapel, 1940s (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Frankfort, KY, Church of the Ascension, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fredericksburg, VA, Saint George's Episcopal Church, 1940s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - F, Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Galveston, TX, Northern, Mary Moody, with Swain Restoration Company, Inc., 1970s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Glendale, CA Forest Lawn Memorial Park, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
  - Gloucester, MA, Saint John's Church, 1950s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gloucester, MA and Newfoundland, Mrs. Spencer Lake, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Grand Rapids, MI, East Congregational Church, 1930s-1950s (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Grand Rapids, MI, South Congregational Church, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - G, Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
  - Hamburg, NY, Hamburg Methodist Church, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hamilton, MA, Christ Church, 1920s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Hamilton, MA, Church of Saint Paul, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hartford, CT, Emanuel Lutheran Church, 1950s (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Holyoke, MA, Mount Holyoke College, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Holyoke, MA, Our Lady of Perpetual Help Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Holyoke, MA, Providence Mother House Chapel, 1930s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Honolulu, HI, Central Union Church, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Houston, TX, Saint Stephen's Episcopal Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Houston, TX, Saint Vincent de Paul Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Huntingdon, PA, Abbey Reformed Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - H, Miscellaneous, 1930s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - I, Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Joseph G. Reynolds Associates, 1920s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - J-K, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Keene, NH, Saint James Episcopal Church, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, MA, Central Methodist Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Leominster, MA, Pilgrim Congregational Church, 1940s (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Lewes, DE, Saint Peter's Episcopal Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Litchfield, CO, Saint Michael's Parish, 1940s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Lonsdale, RI, Christ Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Saint Vincent's Church, 1920s-1930s (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - L, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
  - Manchester, NH, Grace Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Marlborough, MA, First Congregational Church, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Mechanicville, NY, Saint Luke's Episcopal Church, 1930s-1940s (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Millis, MA, Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Millwood, Virginia, Christ Church, 1940s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Milton, MA, Milton Academy, 1940s (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Minneapolis, MN, Saint Mary's Church, Collis Hardenbergh, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Montgomery, AL, Church of the Ascension, 1940s (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Montpelier, VT, Saint Augustine's Church, 1930s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Morgantown, WV, Trinity Episcopal Church, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Muncie, IN, Wearly Monuments, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - M, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
  - Needham, MA, Christ Episcopal Church, 1930s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - New Bedford, MA, Saint Andrew's Church, 1940s (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - New Haven, CT, Evergreen Cemetery Chapel, 1940s (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - New Orleans, LA, Christ Church Cathedral, 1950s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 34-35)
  - New York, NY, Calvary Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 36-37)
  - New York, NY, Cathedral of Saint John the Divine, 1920s-1940s; 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1-11)
  - New York, NY, Church of the Epiphany, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - New York, NY, Church of the Heavenly Rest, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - New York, NY, Riverside Church, 1920s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
  - New York, NY, Saint Thomas Chapel, 1920s-1930s (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Newport, RI, Saint George's School Chapel, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Newton, MA, Grace Church, 1940s-1970s (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Newton Highlands, MA, Saint Paul's Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Norfolk, VA, Holy Trinity Church, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk, VA, Naval Operating Base, Our Lady of Victory Chapel, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
  - North Adams, MA, Saint John's Church, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - North Andover, MA, Merrimack College, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - North Saugus, MA, North Saugus Union Church, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Norwalk, CT, Saint Paul's Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Norwich, CT, Christ Church, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Notre Dame, IN, Holy Cross Seminary, 1920s-1930s (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - N, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
  - Orleans, MA, Methodist Church, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - O, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Pascoag, RI, Calvary Church, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Peabody, MA, Saint Paul's Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Peoria, IL, Bishop Schlarman Chapel, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Peoria, IL, Saint Mary's Cathedral, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Peoria, IL, Saint Mary's Cathedral, Nave Windows, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 38-39)
  - Peoria, IL, Saint Mary's Cathedral, Saint Thomas More Chapel, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Peoria, IL, Saint Mary's Cathedral, Thomas More Murals, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Philadelphia, PA, Saint-Martin-in-the-Fields Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, East Liberty Presbyterian Church, 1930s (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, East Liberty Presbyterian Church, Mellon Memorial Chapel, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, University of Pittsburgh, Heinz Chapel, 1930s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, University of Pittsburgh, Heinz Chapel Notes and Sketches, 1930s (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Pittsfield, MA, Saint Mary the Morning Star Church, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Plainfield, NJ, Crescent Avenue Presbyterian Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Portland, ME, Trinity Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Portland, OR, Holy Redeemer Church, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Portland, OR, Holy Trinity Church, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Portland, OR, Saint Mary Magdalene Church, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Princeton, NJ, Princeton University Chapel, 1920s-1930s (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Proctor, VT, Union Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Providence, RI, Saint Martin's Church (Box 9)
    - General, 1940s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
    - Aisle, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Altar, 1940s-1950s (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Chapel, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Porch Window, 1940s-1950s (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - West Window, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Providence, RI, Saint Pius Church, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - P, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 24-26)
  - Quincy, MA, Wollaston Methodist Church (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Q, Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Reims, France, Cathedrale de Reims, 1920s-1930s (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Richmond, VA, Saint Paul's Catholic Church, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Rockport, MA, Saint Mary's Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Roslindale, MA, Church of Our Saviour, 1920s-1940s (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - R, Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Saint Augustine, FL, Trinity Church Episcopal, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Saint Louis, MO, Church of Saint Michael and Saint George, 1940s (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Saint Louis, MO, First Congregational Church, 1940s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 36-40)
  - Saint Mary's City, MD, Trinity Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Saint Paul, MN, House of Hope Presbyterian Church, 1940s-1950s (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Salisbury, MD, Saint Peter's Episcopal Church, 1930s-1940s (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - San Rafael, CA, Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, 1930s-1950s (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sioux Falls, SD, First Congregational Church, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Southhampton, NY, Saint Andrew's Dune Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Spartanburg, SC, Episcopal Church of the Advent, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Spotswood, NJ, Saint Peter's Protestant Episcopal Church, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Springfield, MA, Holy Family Church, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Springfield, MA, Hope Congregational Church, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Springfield, MA, Trinity Methodist Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Still River, MA, Immaculate Heart of Mary of Saint Benedict, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - S, Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Taunton, MA, Saint Thomas Episcopal Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - The Plains, Va, Grace Episcopal Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 19-21)
  - Toledo, OH, Hope Lutheran Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Toledo, OH, Saint Michael's in the Hills Episcopal Church, 1950s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
  - Tryon, NC, Tryon Presbyterian Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
  - Tulsa, OK, Trinity Episcopal Church, 1920s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
  - T, Miscellaneous, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Valhalla, NY, Gate of Heaven Cemetery, Kelley Mausoleum, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Versailles, KY, First Christian Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Waban, MA, Union Church, 1930-1960s (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Wakefield, MA, Emmanuel Parish Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Wakefield, MA, Universalist Church, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Wallingford, CT, Choate School, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Washington D. C., American Red Cross Building, 1940s (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Washington D. C., Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Church, 1950s (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Washington D. C., Saint David's, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Washington D. C., Saint Paul's Church, Rock Creek Parish, 1940s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 39-41)
  - Washington D. C., Washington Cathedral (Box 11)
    - General, 1940s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Annunciation Window, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
    - Apse Windows, 1940s (Box 11, Folder 5)